{
    "chain": {
        "prompt": "Hello and welcome to Dillon's CLI Study Tool, what would you like to do? (add/remove/study/modify)\n",
        "responses": [
            {
                "response": "modify",
                "prompt": "Which module would you like to modify? (module_name)\n",
                "key": "modify_module",
                "responses": [
                    {
                        "response": "module_name",
                        "prompt": "What term would you like to modify? (term_name)\n",
                        "key": "modify_term"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "response": "study",
                "prompt": "What module would you like to study? (module_name)\n",
                "key": "study"
            },
            {
                "response": "add",
                "prompt": "What would you like to add? (module/term)\n",
                "responses": [
                    {
                        "response": "module",
                        "prompt": "What would you like your module to be titled? (module_name)\n",
                        "key": "add_module"
                    },
                    {
                        "response": "term",
                        "prompt": "What module would you like to add to? (module_name)\n",
                        "key": "add_to_module",
                        "responses": [
                            {
                                "response": "module_name",
                                "prompt": "What term would you like to add? (term_name)\n",
                                "key": "add_term"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "response": "remove",
                "prompt": "Would you like to remove a module? (module/term)\n",
                "responses": [
                    {
                        "response": "module",
                        "prompt": "What module would you like to remove? (module_name)\n",
                        "key": "remove_module"
                    },
                    {
                        "response": "term",
                        "prompt": "What module would you like to remove from? (module_name)\n",
                        "key": "remove_from_module",
                        "responses": [
                            {
                                "response": "module_name",
                                "prompt": "What term would you like to remove? (term_name)\n",
                                "key": "remove_term"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
}